Jay
can i sit here
Of course
This was your seat
wow
what is going on
Very nice
It seems that the transfer students have also changed into new uniforms.
Yeah
Even a person like you who has no fashion sense can see it.
It must have been changed
By the way, isn't Nali going to recommend you to be the monitor?
Yeah
We agreed that if I became the squad leader
Will make her the deputy monitor
Is it B?
That's right
This brand also comes with a cigarette pack.
Didn’t South Korea not enter?
Yes, my dad brought it back when he went to France.
By the way, have you called Nali?
She didn't answer
She has been shutting down her phone since yesterday
She's not usually someone who skips classes casually, right?
That's right
Then why didn't she come to school?
Are you sleeping in at home?
how do we know
Didn't you have lunch together yesterday?
She disappeared after that
[Caihua Girls' High School Medical Club
C-Med 2024 new member recruitment]
C-Med
But the elite gathering place of Caihua Girls' High School
Do you want to join too?
Well, I want to apply and have a look
Also, if you want to go to medical school
Joining this kind of club will give you extra points
But not everyone can enter here.
The threshold is very high
Didn't Jay tell you?
I heard that third graders cannot join
I've heard
Only first-year freshmen will be recruited this year
But I still want to apply and see
You do it because the president is your friend
Do you think you can go through the back door?
what
But it's weird
Na Li also said before that she wanted to join this club.
so
Think about it carefully
one person missing
It will also be less competitive, right?
If there is only one candidate, Xiao Jing
Everyone, please close your eyes quickly and vote with a show of hands.
It's almost midterm exams
teacher
What's wrong
I also want to recommend a candidate for monitor
Really?
Who do you want to recommend?
Yu Seqi sitting next to me
Yu Seqi
Do you want to be monitor?
Of course
I promised Seulgi if she becomes the monitor
I will help her vigorously
Then there's nothing we can do
Come vote, everyone, take out your notebooks
Cui Jing one vote
Yu Seqi one vote
Invalid vote
[Choi Jung: 11 votes Woo Seul Gi: 11 votes
Invalid votes: 1]
Yu Seqi
Congratulations Seulgi
Congratulations
Hello Zhao Yaluo
Are you sure you didn't issue the wrong ticket?
I want to see it with my own eyes
[Yu Seqi]
Hey, take out your notebook and let me take a look.
what
Where did you tear up the paper to vote?
Hello Cui Jing
Is there anything wrong with voting?
Do you dare to ask?
You also think it’s strange that you would choose the monitor, right?
so
Someone tampered
Someone must have changed the votes.
Look at these votes for you
All ripped from the same notebook
It was written by the same person
There was a black box operation in this election
do you mean...
I can't get everyone's support
But there is a way to collude with everyone
Do you want to do black box work for me?
Of course you can't
So do you think someone is secretly helping me?
Cui Jing, stop making trouble
I know it too
People don’t vote for me because they like me.
After all, I'm just a guy from the countryside
Just a bumpkin with no background
Xiaojing, stop making trouble
Then Seulgi will be the monitor and you will be the deputy monitor.
This will also give you extra points when applying to schools.
Teacher, I think Cui Jing should apologize.
why should i apologize
Because you refuse to accept the result
And humiliated Seulgi in public
He even questioned his classmates
Of course you should apologize
right
monitor
Yeah
I hope you can apologize to everyone
Sorry, I lost my temper
what are you doing
[Jay]
Now that you've become the squad leader, it's time for a treat.
[Yu Seqi]
Sorry, I lost my temper
Please knock on the door before coming in
Although I don’t know what tricks you are up to
but get out of the way
Mom has to work
Please go home and take a shower first
I chose the monitor today.
"Yu Seqi"
Is she the monitor of your class?
Can you please stop thinking you know everything?
Do you have to ask questions as carefully as if you were handling a case?
Damn it
Hello Cui Jing
I didn't ask you to be the squad leader, did I?
Who are you taking your anger out on now?
Lawyer Nam Ji-yeon who was class president every year during her student days
How can you understand my mood?
I'll take a shower first
Get it done before I come back. Go back to your room.
Damn it
The Evaluation and Supervisory Yuan should also take some measures.
OK I got it
It seems that he will be prosecuted
sorry
Give some settlement money
Convince family members to sign a settlement agreement
Is this so difficult?
A single mother with a child probably needs money very much, right?
If you can suppress the media
In fact, delaying time is not a bad thing
After all, you have to prove medical negligence.
almost impossible
Who said it was a fault
The patient's heartbeat had stopped before arriving at the hospital
How many times do you want me to say it?
The hospital has tried its best to rescue the patients
Yes I will pay attention to my words
Remember every word you say
All represent the position of the hospital
And this matter cannot be delayed
Must negotiate a reconciliation
Don’t just give people money
Yes I know
I will find a way to convince the family members
Okay, you can go out now
Yes
By the way, Dean, there's one more thing
There is a shortage of medicines
Most of the medicines are self-paid
The unit price is not low either…
Don't worry about this kind of thing
Even if there is a thief
After all, we are one of our own, right?
I turned a blind eye to the mistakes my family made
Just pretend you don't know
OK
[Dean Liu Taijun]
So Nally's mother
I really sold the house at a low price.
How much did it sell for
3.7 billion won
(Note: Approximately NT$79 million)
Oh my god, did you sell it for 300 million won?
(Note: Approximately NT$6.4 million)
It seems that she is really in a hurry for money
But why are they suddenly selling their house?
Isn’t their daughter a senior in high school?
The real estate agent said they were looking at houses in other areas.
Seems like planning to move away
Please use it slowly
I said I’d treat you to a fancy restaurant
Why come to the pizza place?
How come? I love the pizza in this store the most.
Savory spicy sausage with rich sauce
Great for eating with dip
Have another cold Coke
Are you because your mother is afraid of your allergies?
I won’t let you eat it, so you think it’s delicious, right?
But Jai, why don’t you eat?
I'm leaving soon
Do you have an appointment with anyone?
Could it be with Yu Seulgi?
If you ask too many questions, you will lose your charm.
Jay, couldn’t you...
Are you really interested in Seulgi?
Jay
Besides paper cranes, do you also fold anything else?
Anything else?
What do you want me to fold?
[Coin-operated KTV]
♫No one ever told me that♫
♫Would you like to come closer♫
♫Let’s just wait like this♫
♫Why did I meet you♫
♫Where should I go now♫
You also know this song
Well, I have Lucid Fall at home
All albums by Misoni
Are you his biggest fan?
But your voice sings this song better
what
I said you have a nice voice
very sweet
Xiao Jing seems to be very disappointed
Will your relationship get worse because of me?
You don't need to care
We're not very good to begin with, you know that, right?
But you want to join the medical society
Maybe not that easy
Cui Jing would probably object
Also
The air at night is so good
Fortunately the rain stopped
I thought you wouldn't come
why
I made you wait too long and you're angry
No
Just…
It's easy for everyone to forget me
So I don’t really wait for anyone.
I don't like waiting for people
I don’t know how others are doing
But I do what I say
You must wait for me
Although I might be a little late
Seulgi
Let's go back to my house together
Now?
Yeah, let's go back to my house together
chat
Sleep together and then go to school together tomorrow
How is it? Not bad, right?
How
Are you afraid that your mother will not be allowed?
Do you want me to call you?
No
She doesn't really care what time I get back.
Then it's not bad, right?
Let's go back to my house
Arrived
Hello
Does it scare you?
This is my brother Jieyin
Hi Jieyin, how are you?
You ran into sister Jenna's room again
Say it quickly
I thought you were an only child
You also have a sister
But she's gone now
Sorry, did I ask something I shouldn't have asked...
Not the kind that passes away
Although it is possible that she really passed away
what
Come in, this is my room
Jay
What's wrong
It's like the bottom of the sea here
I've scuba dived before when I traveled
Others say the seabed is scary
But I feel relaxed instead
In silence…
The bottom of the sea where you can’t even see your fingers
How to describe that feeling?
It feels like returning to my mother's belly
Yes, that's the feeling
I feel like I'm the only one left in the world
But not lonely at all
On the contrary, I feel very safe and comfortable
Although I have never dived
But I seem to understand
Let's go together next time
You will also like it
Hello
Alas
what are you doing again
I also had an identical skirt
It seems that you also liked to play princess when you were a child.
I shouldn't like it
dad
mom
I didn't expect you to have that kind of past
But how could that be your fault
not your fault
The adults should be blamed for not taking good care of their children.
Thank you for telling me this
unspeakable things
Actually…
I also have something I want to surrender to.
what
Actually, I’m not a big fan of Lucid Fall.
Because my sister likes it
I've only listened to a few of his songs
No wonder…
I feel strange
thank you…
tell me honestly
Okay, let's get ready for bed.
Is this your first time?
what
Take a shower with friends
That's not... that's not the case
You feel cuter in the water
Why are you so red?
Maybe soaked for too long
a bit hot
You shouldn't be thinking of anything strange, right?
What...what's weird
For example, something like this
[Jin Nali]
I will apologize to Seulgi myself
I'll just transfer schools
As long as I transfer to another school
You will delete that video
Please reply to me
Jay
i was wrong
Please, you must delete that video
[Litigation Application Case Records]
[Complaint]
The deceased Yu Daohe
He was sent to J Medical Center due to abdominal pain.
[Death diagnosis certificate]